DANIEL WESTBROOK

Front End Web Developer and Designer

Mobile: (+61) 402 697 455 Email: westy12dan@gmail.com Website: westbrookdaniel.com 27 Peasholm Street,

27 Peasholm Street City Beach, WA

About Me

I enjoy formulating innovative solutions for Perth businesses and agencies with strategic design thinking. Developing an Designing have been passions of mine for a long time, and I have enjoyed professional experience in both. I always look for new challenges and ways I can develop my knowledge of the latest technologies and methods.

Find out more about me and my projects at westbrookdaniel.com

Employment History

Jun 2020 - Now Front End Developer

Unearthed Solutions unearthed.solutions

Feb 2019 - Now Website Developer and Graphic Designer

Eclipse Design Solutions www.eclipsedesigns.com.au

Aug 2019 - Now Web Designer and Developer Contractor

Be Media <u>www.bemedia.com.au</u>

2014 - 2017 Hockey W.A. Coaching

Perth Hockey Stadium, Bentley WA 6102

Education

2018 - 2020 Bachelor of Arts at Curtin University

Digital Design, Creative Advertising and Graphic Design

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020 Digital Marketing Internship at Be Media Perth

1/1122 Hay St, West Perth WA 6005

Nov 2018 Shortlisted for the Charlie Bell Scholarship

for Future Leaders 2019

Apr 2018 - Aug 2018 Web Internship at Be Media Perth

1/1122 Hay St, West Perth WA 6005

Jan 2018 Awarded Curtin Excellence Scholarship 2018

2001 - 2017 Sacred Heart College, 15 Hocking Parade, Sorrento WA

Received ATAR: 91.55

Development

- JS Frameworks (React)
- HTML CSS JavaScript
- CSS Frameworks
- Wordpress Development
- · Version Management (Git, Github)
- Express and Node.js
- And Lots More

Skills and Abilities

- Excellent computing and design knowledge
- Great communication and interpersonal skills
- Reliable, punctual and diligent
- Experience working in a team environment and independently
- Excellent attention to detail with strong problem solving ability

Interests

- Graphic Design
- Creative and Visual Arts
- · Sport (tennis, hockey)
- Music and Guitar
- · Video Games

References

Bill Heppard Web Project Manager BirdBrain

3/73 Troy Terrace, Jolimont WAhone: Mobile: 0412 461 706

Daniel Brouse
Designer / Director
DB Digital Creative
Perth WA, Australia
Mobile: 0412 461 706